nature-pictures.org 2016-03-05

# Privacy policy / Polityka prywatności

**Privacy policy**

**The privacy of our visitors**

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our websites, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/)

**Polityka prywatności**

Polityka Prywatności serwisu internetowego wzgledem odwiedzających uzytkowników.

Wyświetlamy pochodzące z Google AdSense reklamy, które stanowią niezależną część prezentowanych serwisów. Program Google AdSense może wykorzystywać pliki cookie oraz inne sygnalizatory WWW, które w momencie wyświetlania reklam na naszej stronie spowodują przesłanie reklamodawcom informacji o dostawcy internetu, adres IP, rodzaj przeglądarki, informację o zainstalowaniu dodatku Flash osoby przgladajacej nasze serwisy. Na ogół jest to używane do dobierania reklam na podstawie stron, które inetrnauci odwiedzili wcześniej lub do dobierania reklam lokalnych powiązanych z lokalizacją osoby przeglądajacej serwisy.

Do celów analizy ruchu internetowego gromadzone są dane plików z logami czyli numer IP, nazwa sieciowa komputera , dostawca Internetu, rodzaj przeglądarki internetowej z której użytkownik korzysta, czas spędzony na stronie oraz informacje o ruchu wewnątrz serwisu.

Zebrane informacje slużą do serwowania reklam lub analizy ruchu i nie są przekazywane innym podmiotom.

W opcjach przeglądarki internetowej można całkowicie wyłączyć lub zdezaktywować pliki cookies na naszych stronach lub stronach naszych reklamodawców, można też blokować pobieranie plików cookie stosując programy typu firewall.   
Wyłączenie plików cookie może jednak spowodować niemożliwość pełnego wykorzystania opcji naszego serwisu. 

Polityka prywatności zgodna z AdSense.
